Guide to the New York State Agricultural Experiment Station records, 1859-2008
New York State Agricultural Experiment Station records, 1859-2008
- A Visit by Vice-President Sproull, Provost Corson and Deal Palm..., October 18, 1966 (Box 126, Folder 28)
- Agreements, Contracts, Leases, 1903-1929 (Box 127, Folder 1)
- Agreements, Contracts, Leases, 1922-1942 (Box 127, Folder 2)
- Agreements, Contracts, Leases (Box 127, Folder 3)
- Current Contacts and Leases (Box 127, Folder 4)
- Financial Reports, 1885-1928 (Box 127, Folder 5)
- Military Absence and Appointments, 1940-1941 (Box 127, Folder 6)
- Military Deferments, April 1943 (Box 127, Folder 7)
- Military Deferments of Men over 38, 1945-1948 (Box 127, Folder 8)
- Military Service, 1942-1945 (Box 127, Folder 9)
- Old Grant and Investigatorship Records I (Box 127, Folder 10)
- Old Grant and Investigatorship Records II (Box 127, Folder 11)
- Payments on Contracts for Horticulture Building, 1931-32 (Box 127, Folder 12)
- Records Meeting-Executive Committee American Agriculture Colleges and Experiment Stations, 1914-1919 (Box 127, Folder 13)
- State Board Files, 1912-1918 (Box 127, Folder 14)
- Statements Requested by Director Heinicke, 1944 (Box 127, Folder 15)
- US Government-Congress Bills, Acts, etc. (Box 127, Folder 16)
- Apple Research and Development Program (ARDP)-Papers, Research Proposals, March 10, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 1)
- ARD, March 10, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 2)
- Apple Research and Development Program (ARDP)-Papers, Research Proposals, March 10, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 1)
- ARDP-Memoranda, Correspondence, March 10, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 2)
- ARDP-Meeting with Board of Directors, November 24, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 3)
- ARDP-Research Proposals, March 5, 1993 (Box 129, Folder 4)
- ARDP-Correspondence, March 5, 1993 (Box 129, Folder 5)
- ARDP-Board Meeting, March 17, 1994 (Box 129, Folder 6)
- ARDP-Meeting, Correspondence, November 14-15, 1994 (Box 129, Folder 7)
- ARDP-Meeting RSVP'S, Correspondence, November 23, 1993 (Box 129, Folder 8)
- Corporate Liaison Group Meeting-Proposals, 1993-1994 (Box 129, Folder 9)
- Director's Correspondence, 1985-1994 (Box 129, Folder 10)
- Apple Research Association Meeting, February 19-21, 1991 (Box 129, Folder 11)
- Apple Research Association Meeting, March 21, 1991 (Box 129, Folder 12)
- Apple Research Association Meeting-Correspondence, 1974-1992 (Box 129, Folder 13)
- ARDP-Advisory Board Meeting, 1994-1995 (Box 129, Folder 14)
- New York State Beet Research Association Meeting, January 16, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 15)
- New York State Beet Research Association Meeting, January 15, 1993 (Box 129, Folder 16)
- New York State Cabbage Advisory Committee Meeting, December 3, 1991 (Box 129, Folder 17)
- Cabbage Research Association Meeting, December 3, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 18)
- Cabbage Meeting, December, 1993 (Box 129, Folder 19)
- Cabbage Advisory Committee Meeting, December 7, 1993 (Box 129, Folder 20)
- Cabbage Research Association-1995 Proposals, December 7, 1994 (Box 129, Folder 21)
- Pea Advisory Committee Meeting, December 9, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 22)
- Pea Advisory Committee, June 15, 1905 (Box 129, Folder 23)
- New York State Pea Advisory Committee Meeting, November 29, 1994 (Box 129, Folder 24)
- New York State Snap Bean Advisory Committee Meeting, 1991 (Box 129, Folder 25)
- New York State Snap Bean Advisory Committee Meeting, 1991 (Box 129, Folder 26)
- New York State Snap Bean Research Association Meeting, November 15, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 27)
- New York State Snap Bean Research Association Meeting, November 15, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 28)
- New York State Snap Bean Research Association Meeting, November 19, 1993 (Box 129, Folder 29)
- New York State Snap Bean Research Association Meeting, November 19, 1993 (Box 129, Folder 30)
- New York State Snap Bean Advisory Committee, November 17, 1994 (Box 129, Folder 31)
- New York State Processing Sweet Corn Advisory Committee, December 4, 1991 (Box 129, Folder 32)
- Sweet Corn Research Association Meeting, December 1, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 33)
- Sweet Corn Meeting, December 1, 1993 (Box 129, Folder 34)
- Sweet Corn Research Association, December 1, 1993 (Box 129, Folder 35)
- Sweet Corn-Research Proposals, December 1, 1994 (Box 129, Folder 36)
- New York State Tomato Research Association Meeting, December 12, 1991 (Box 129, Folder 37)
- New York State Tomato Research Association Meeting, December 10, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 38)
- New York State Tomato Research Association Meeting, December 9, 1993 (Box 129, Folder 39)
- New York State Tomato Research Association Meeting, December 8, 1994 (Box 129, Folder 40)
- Northeast Region 87-Annual Meeting (Regional Research Project), August 17-19, 1991 (Box 130, Folder 1)
- Northeast Region 87-Annual Meeting (Regional Research Project), August 8-10, 1992 (Box 130, Folder 2)
- Northeast Region 87-Annual Meeting (Regional Research Project), August 8-10, 1992 (Box 130, Folder 3)
- Northeast Region 103-Technical Committee Meeting (Regional Research Project), June 28-29, 1988 (Box 130, Folder 4)
- Northeast Region 103-Technical Committee Meeting (Regional Research Project), June 28-29, 1988 (Box 130, Folder 5)
- Northeast Region 103-Technical Committee Meeting (Regional Research Project), June 10-13, 1989 (Box 130, Folder 6)
- Northeast Region 103-Technical Committee Meeting (Regional Research Project), October, 1990-December, 1990 (Box 130, Folder 7)
- Northeast Region 103-Technical Committee Meeting (Regional Research Project), 1991 (Box 130, Folder 8)
- Northeast Region 103-Technical Committee Meeting (Regional Research Project), 1992 (Box 130, Folder 9)
- Northeast Region 103-Technical Committee Meeting-Correspondence (Regional Research Project), 1992-1993 (Box 130, Folder 10)
- Northeast Region 103-Technical Committee Meeting-Correspondence (Regional Research Project), 1993-1995 (Box 130, Folder 11)
- Northeast Region 107-Annual Meeting (Regional Research Project), January 16, 1993 (Box 130, Folder 12)
- Northeast Region 139 (Regional Research Project), 1983-1988 (Box 130, Folder 13)
- Northeast Region 141 (Regional Research Project), 1986-1993 (Box 130, Folder 14)
- New York Agricultural Experiment Station-Policy and Regulations, April, 1907 (Box 130, Folder 15)
- Register of Staff and Employees, 1884-1927 (Box 130, Folder 16)
- Horticultural Science Library Notebook Listing the Books Owned and Wanted by the Departments, 1908-1913 (Box 130, Folder 17)
- Horticultural Science - Pomology and Viticulture Dept. Library - Correspondence, 1970s (Box 136, Folder 12)
- Record of Research Work of Individual Members of the Staff (copy in eCommons), 1923-1928 (Box 130, Folder 18-19)
- Geneva Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1961-1972 (Box 130, Folder 21)
- Geneva Staff Meeting Minutes, 1925-1929 (Box 130, Folder 22)
- Geneva Staff Meeting Minutes, 1930-1932 (Box 130, Folder 23)
- Horticultural Science Department Ledgers-27 Ledgers, 1923-1936 (Box 131)
- Plaque-Station Team, Awarded First Place Silver Cup in YMCA Corporate Sports Challenge, "1996 Finger Lakes Corporate Cup Champions"; List of Team Members Included, 1996 (Box 132)
- Employee Handbook, no date (Box 136, Folder 7)
- Geneva Library Serials List, 1994 (Box 136, Folder 19)
- Geneva Library - Borrowing Ledgers, 1945-1952 (Box 136)
- Experiment Station Club Play "A Joke on Santa Claus", no date (Box 136, Folder 2)
- Prince Nurseries sales ledger, Flushing, New York, 1820s-1850s (Box 138)
- Small Prince Nurseries sales ledger, Flushing, New York, 1836-1837 (Box 138)
- Record Book of Grapes ledger, 1859 (Box 138)
  Also contains listings for strawberries, chrysanthemums, peaches, carnations, raspberries, phlox, gladiolus, and some others. Quite possibly from Prince Nursery, Flushing New York
- Linnean Botanical Garden sales ledger, Flushing, New York, 1831-1833 (Box 138)
- Series II Departments and Centers
- Fruit breeding records and the history of working with vinifera, hybrid, and native grape varieties and documents concerning the wax model collection., 1890s-1917 (Box 139-141)
- Correspondence and Dictation Notebooks in Shorthand, 1882-1887 (Box 197)
- Labor Book, 1882 (Box 197)
- Day Book, 1882 (Box 197)
- Experiment Record Books, 1882; 1883 (Box 197)
- Labor Receipts, 1883-1884 (Box 197)
- Field Plats - three notebooks, 1884-1885 (Box 197)
- Calves Ledger, 1885 (Box 197)
- Cattle Experiments - Ledger, 1885 (Box 197)
- Ledger, 1895 (Box 197)
- Catalogue of Cereals (Box 197)
- Records of the Computer Center at Geneva, 1973-2008 (Box 142)
- Series III. Buildings
- Papers Pertaining to Cattle Barn (Box 122, Folder 25)
- Papers Pertaining to Repairs of Administration Building (Box 122, Folder 26)
- NYSAES Open House, 1925, 1963, 1976 (Box 94)
- Dedication of Food Science Building, 1960 (Box 94)
- Dedication of Food Science building, 1960 (Box 92)
- Food Research Program and Building, 1960 (Box 136, Folder 11)
- Dedication of Hudson Valley Lab, 1964, 1973 (Box 94)
- Dedication of the Sturtevant Hotel, 1964 (Box 94)
- Sturtevant Hall (seed investigations) (Box 123, Folder 21)
- Dedication-Sturtevant Hall, 1964 (Box 123, Folder 22)
- Dedication-Sturtevant Hall, 1964 (Box 123, Folder 23)
- Dedication Proceedings-Sturtevant Hall, 1964 (Box 123, Folder 24)
- Entomology - Plant Pathology Dedication, 1969 (Box 94)
- Entomology-Plant Pathology Building (Box 126, Folder 8)
- Naming of Hedrick Hall, Carriage House (Box 125, Folder 29)
- Parrot Hall Project (Box 123, Folder 17)
- Plans of Director's Residence, NYSAES
  - 3 plans of Director's Residence, NYSAES
    - Attic, Floor Plan (Map-case *, Folder 2)
    - Transverse Section (Map-case *, Folder 2)
    - Longitudinal Section (Map-case *, Folder 2)
  - 9 plans of Director's Residence, NYSAES
    - 1st floor (Map-case *, Folder 2)
    - 2nd floor
    - Attic (Map-case *, Folder 2)
    - East elevation (Map-case *, Folder 2)
    - North elevation (Map-case *, Folder 2)
    - South elevation (Map-case *, Folder 2)
    - West elevation (Map-case *, Folder 2)
    - Longitudinal section (Map-case *, Folder 2)
    - Transverse section (Map-case *, Folder 2)
- Series IV. Centennial and Other Anniversaries
- Centennial Celebration of Agricultural Experiment Stations, 1875-1975 (Box 123, Folder 2)
- Centennial Celebration of Agricultural Experiment Stations, 1875-1975 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Photographs--Unidentified
- "Entomology Reaches It's 100th Birthday", 1954 (Box 124, Folder 13)
- 75th Anniversary materials, 1957 (Box 92)
- 75th Anniversary NYSAES, 1957 (Box 94)
- 'The Geneva Times' 75th Anniversary Section, October 4, 1957 (Box 119, Folder 3)
- 75th Anniversary of Station, Farm Research, January 1957 (Box 125, Folder 44)
- Articles About Agricultural Experiment Station, 100th Anniversary (Box 124, Folder 2)
- Centennial Vegetable Garden, 1976 (Box 123, Folder 5)
- Centennial Garden, 1976 (Box 94)
- Centennial Celebration items: book, button, handouts, 1981-1982 (Box 93)
- Centennial 1982, Symposium (Box 123, Folder 4)
- Centennial, Agricultural Experiment Station, Geneva, New York, 1982 (Box 123, Folder 1)
- Centennial Celebration, 1982 (Box 94)
- Open House 1982 Centennial Celebration (Box 123, Folder 15)
- Resolution Honoring 100th Anniversary, By Geneva City Council, September 1, 1982 (Box 120, Folder 1)
- Calendar - Centennial, 1982 (Box 134)
- Centennial Slide Presentation, 1982 (Box 128)
- 125th Anniversary Event - flyers, brochures, articles and DVD (DVD #1760)of 125 Years in Pictures, 2007 (Box 136, Folder 17)
- 125th Anniversary - Posters, 2007 (Box 134)
- Series V. Awards and Diplomas
  - #1-6 having same illustration showing Columbia presenting a torch and the world to a man and a woman.
  - Gold Medal (Map-case *, Folder 1)
    1. United States of America Universal Exposition, St. Louis, MDCCCCIV (1904), commemorating the Acquisition of the Louisiana Territory. The International Jury of Awards has conferred a GOLD MEDAL upon the Department of Animal Husbandry, New York Agricultural Experiment Station, Geneva, New York. Charts and Graphic Representation of Investigation of Sources of Milk Fat.
  - SILVER MEDAL (Map-case *, Folder 1)
    2. (same as above) SILVER MEDAL - Tomatoes
  - BRONZE MEDAL (Map-case *, Folder 1)
    3. (same as above) BRONZE MEDAL - Bacteriological Department New York Agricultural Experiment Station; Models and drawings showing Investigational Results with the Cause and Control of Rusty Spot in Cheddar Cheese.
  - GOLD MEDAL (Map-case *, Folder 1)
    4. (same as above) GOLD MEDAL - Chemical Department, N.Y. Ag Exp. Station; Charts showing effect of temperature and of paraffining cheese upon yield and quality of cheese in curing.
  - GRAND PRIZE (Map-case *, Folder 1)
    5. (same as above) GRAND PRIZE - Department of Horticulture, N.Y. Ag. Exp. Station; Wax models and photographs illustrating results of investigation into self-fertility of the grape and correlation between seed character and seedling character by S.A. Beach.
  - COMMEMORATIVE DIPLOMA (Map-case *, Folder 1)
    6. (same as above) COMMEMORATIVE DIPLOMA - W.H. Jordan, Chairman, Exposition Committee of the Association of American Agricultural Colleges and Experimental Stations, (and letter sending this award)
  - MEDAILLE D'OR (Map-case *, Folder 1)
    7. Republique Francais, Ministere du commerce, d'l'Industrie des Postes et des Telegraphes Exposition Universekkede 1900; MEDAILLE D'OR - N.Y. State Ag. Exp. Station Group VIII -Classe 45
  - UN PREMIER PRIX (Map-case *, Folder 1)
    8. (same as above) (2 copies) UN PREMIER PRIX - Arbres Frutiers and Fruits 22/1/44 9. Letter: St. Louis Expo to NYSAES; "Please find herewith a diploma of the award conferred upon you by the Superior Jury of Awards connected with the Louisiana Purchase Expo of 1904"
  - St. Louis Expo (Map-case *, Folder 1)
    9. Letter: St. Louis Expo to NYSAES; "Please find herewith a diploma of the award conferred upon you by the Superior Jury of Awards connected with the Louisiana Purchase Expo of 1904"
- Series VI. Films and Videos
  - 16mm Film, "Spraying and Controlling Orchard Pests" - Humble Oil and Refining Co., 1966 (Box 96)
  - TV film strip of Director Donald Barton, Dr. Freeman Lester McEwen, and Dr. James Hamilton Concerning the new entomology and plant pathology building., November 30, 1966 (Box 128)
  - Insect Pheromone Flight (Box 128)
  - Tunnel Film-Wendell Roelofs (Box 128)
  - Flight Tunnel - W. Roelofs, F-1047 (Box 137)
  - Grape Production, V-5392 (Box 137)
  - Station Picnic, 1946-1947; V-5393 (Box 137)
  - A Tour of New York State Agricultural Station, 1989; V-5394 (Box 137)
  - Aerial of Station, July 30, 1990; V-5395 (Box 137)
  - Governor's Visit - Master, August 25, 1992; V-5396 (Box 137)
  - New York State Horticulture Society - Stone Fruit Topics, 1997; V-5397 (Box 137)
  - Aerial Footage of NYSAES, October 9, 1997; V-5398 (Box 137)
  - Apple Cider Processing Seminar - 1 of 3, March 7, 1997; V-5399 (Box 137)
  - Apple Cider Processing Seminar - 2 of 3, March 7, 1997; V-5400 (Box 137)
  - Apple Cider Processing Seminar - 3 of 3, March 7, 1997; V-5401 (Box 137)
  - Grape Conservation Practices - S-VHS Master, October 1999; V-5402 (Box 137)
  - Grape Conservation Practices - Backup Master, October 1999; V-5403 (Box 137)
  - From the Farm to Your Fork: The Geneva Station Means Business for New York, V-5404 (Box 137)
  - Bob Anderson - Pear Pruning - Master, V-5405 (Box 137)
  - Dr. Gerald Marx - Pea Time Lapse, F-1039 (Box 137)
  - Frost Resistant Tomato, F-1040 and F-1045 (Box 137)
  - Moth Flight Chamber, F-1041 (Box 137)
  - no title, F-1042 (Box 137)
  - "500,000 to 1" - Sinclair Refining Company, New York City, F-1043 (Box 137)
  - Mechanical Harvesting, F-1044 (Box 137)
  - Sex Attractants, April, 1967; F-1046 (Box 137)
  - Governor George Pataki's Visit, September 4, 1997, Sept. 4, 1997; V-844, V-9204 (Box 143)
    Two copies
  - "Career Development" Orientation Seminar, no date; V-845 (Box 143)
  - IR4 Seminar: Director's Office, Bob Holm, July 23, 1999; V-9205 (Box 143)
  - Senator Nozzolio: Cornell University and Ag. Tech. Park Colloquium (1 of 2), Feb. 10, 2005; V-9206 (Box 143)
  - Senator Nozzolio: Cornell University and Ag. Tech. Park Colloquium (2 of 2), Feb. 10, 2005; V-9207 (Box 143)
  - Preparing for the Next Century: A Look at Cornell's College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, Oct., 2005; V-9208 (Box 143)
  - Impact of Outreach and Applied Research, c. 2005; V-9209 (Box 143)
    "from Thomas Henick-Kling"
  - The Land Grant System in a Changing World: Perceptions, Images, and Reputation as Seen by an Outsider, no date; V-9210 (Box 143)
  - Pesticide Building Decomission, Feb. 11, 1994 to Feb. 21, 1994, Feb. 11-21, 1994; V-9211 (Box 143)
  - Land Grant Universities Program #2, no date; V-9212 (Box 143)
  - 21st Century Faculty Responsibility, no date; V-9213 (Box 143)
  - Associated New York State Food Processors, Inc., and T.G.T., no date; V-9214 (Box 143)
  - Robert A. Plane Retirement, June 28, 1990; V-9215 (Box 143)
- Series VII. Photographs and Slides
- Views of the Collective Exhibit of the Colleges of Agriculture and Mechanic Arts and Experiment Stations in the Palace of Education, Louisiana Purchase Exposition, 1904 (Box 136, Folder 20)
- Photographs used in experiment station bulletins, including photographs of Native American women taken by Jessie Tarbox Beals, regarded as the first woman press photographer., 1915 (Box 128, Folder 1)
- Photographs, Mounted: (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Barton Hall, Aerial Views, Farm Scenes
- Glass and Regular Slides: 1959-1965 (Air Dusting, Resistance): (Box 120)
  - Chinese Pheromone Delegation, 1973
  - ULV Slides: Spraying, Early Agriculture Slides, IPM Slides
- Photograph, probably of New York State Agricultural Experiment Station staff members (Box 93)
- Photograph of a letter from A.B. Cornell to the president of the New York State Agricultural Society, July 7, 1880 (Box 93)
- Photographic Record Book, includes portraits of staff NYSAES members, 1924 (Box 97)
- Unidentified Photos (Box 123)
- Photos (Box 125, Folder 34-35)
- About the Experiment Station (Narratives, Slide Show), 1982 (Box 94)
- Employee Recognition Events, 1961-1994 (Box 134)
- Experiment Stations - Oversized Photos, including Aerials, 1900s-1990s (Box 134)
- Grape Field (Box 136, Folder 22)
- NYSAES Greenhouse - Phil Forsline, Herb Aldwinckle, Susan Brown, Harvey Reissig (Box 134)
- NYSAES Food Science Building - Processing Plant - Donald Barton's Lab, Malcomb Bourne (Box 136, Folder 21)
- Series VIII. Publications/Publicity
- Preparation of Bulletins; Pertaining to Mailing Lists (Box 122, Folder 27)
- From the book "The Vegetables of New York", The Cucurbits part IV, galley proofs annotated by U.P. Hedrick and F. H. Hall, 1928 (Box 133)
- Printed material, no date (Box 92)
- History of the Mills Family "By Way of Introduction" (Box 124, Folder 26)
- Mycology drawings - W.D. Mills (Box 124, Folder 27)
- History of Mycology - by H.M. Fitzpatrick, April 29, 1929 (Box 124, Folder 28)
- Works by Mills, 1929 (Box 124, Folder 34)
- Index of Bulletins and Circulars, produced by NYSAES Faculty, 1885-1968 (Box 130, Folder 24)
- Fruit and Vegetable Books Available at the NYSAES and list of what was sold, 1930s-1960s (Box 136, Folder 32)
- Index of Publications by NYSAES Faculty (copy in eCommons), 1933-1957 (Box 130, Folder 20)
- Index of Journal Papers by NYSAES Faculty, 1948-1988 (Box 136, Folder 30-31)
- Ledger describing the distribution of NYSAES publications, 1930s-1950s (Box 130, Folder 25)
- Journal of Percival John Parrott's Trip to Africa, 1937 (Box 136, Folder 29)
- History of Appropriations Granted to NYSAES Since 1882, 1944 (Box 136, Folder 1)
- Extension Publications, 1949-1953 (Box 124, Folder 30)
- Files concerning the history of the Station and about the book written by Chapman and Glass, 1955-2000 (Box 124, Folder 25)
- Book plates by Joseph Keplinger, 1960s (Box 136, Folder 23)
- Photo prints used in Bulletin 49- Green Fruitworms, 1974 (Box 136, Folder 34)
- A Plan for the Future, 1984-03 (Box 125, Folder 36)
- Cornell Uncorks The Grape Team, 1998 (Box 136, Folder 25)
- Brochures, Miscellaneous Publications about the Agricultural Experiment Station, Geneva, New York, 1907-2006 (Box 125, Folder 3)
- Articles about the New York State Agricultural Experiment Station, 1940-1997 (Box 136, Folder 26)
- Articles about the New York State Agricultural Experiment Station, 2003-2007 (Box 136, Folder 27)
- Articles about the New York State Agricultural Experiment Station, 2008-2009 (Box 136, Folder 28)
- Research Publications, April 2000 (Box 125, Folder 41)
- Calendar, 2001 (Box 134)
- "Aggie the Ladybug" - a coloring book, no date (Box 136, Folder 24)
- Proofs of Moths, no date (Box 136, Folder 33)
- Proofs of Orchard Mites - Watercolor, no date (Box 136, Folder 35)
- Newspaper Articles (Box 119, Folder 1)
- Series IX. Conferences, Projects, Symposiums
- Phonograph - Transcript of Interview Of "Farm Forum of the Air" on the Anniversary and the Symposium., 1957 (Box 96)
- Symposium Publications, 1957-1969 (Box 123, Folder 25)
- Lime and Filter Conference, July 16-17, 1964 (Box 123, Folder 9)
- Snap Bean Industry Conference, Jordan Hall, March 3, 1966 (Box 125, Folder 45)
- Proceedings-Frontiers in Food Research, June 11-12, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 21)
- Symposium and Dedication, Entomology-Plant Pathology, March 20-21, 1969 (Box 126, Folder 5)
- Symposium on Potentials in Crop Protection, December 1969 (Box 136, Folder 36)
- UC/AID Pest Management Training Workshop, July 18, 1976-August 27, 1976 (Box 125, Folder 46)
- Nutrition Council Seminar, 1977 (Box 136, Folder 37)
- Computer Symposium, January 10, 1989 (Box 126, Folder 4)
- International Projects
- Reports, Addresses and Memos about research projects done in Ghana, Kenya, and Nigeria, 1970-1971 (Box 135)